(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-13T22:04:06.122386",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
In a kingdom far far away,
Where all nyut-nyut lives,
A sudden calamity strikes
among the nyut-nyut who lives in harmony.
A pink giant monster has emerged out of nowhere
and created havoc everywhere.
A lot of buildings and villages were destroyed.
All nyut-nyut were left hopeless
until a mysterious magical squirrel arrived
to find a legendary weapon, the Nut Blade.
The legend said that this mysterious squirrel
will bring an end to this calamity...
強くなれる
To grow stronger...
理由を知った
...I found a reason.
僕を連れて進め
Take me along and move forward!
泥だらけの走馬灯に酔う
Drowning in a muddy kaleidoscope of memories,
こわばる心 震える手は
my tense heart and shaking hands
掴みたいものがある
hold onto something they want to grasp.
それだけさ
That's all there is to it.
夜の匂いに
In the scent of the night,
空睨んでも
even if I stare up at the sky,
変わっていけるのは自分自身だけ
the only one who can change is myself.
それだけさ
That's all there is to it.
強く成れる理由を知った
I learned the reason to become strong.
僕を連れて進め
Take me along and push forward!
どうしたって!
No matter what!
消せない夢も 止まれない今も
With dreams I can't erase and a present I can't stop,
誰かのために強くなれるなら
if I can grow stronger for someone else's sake,
ありがとう 悲しみよ
thank you, sadness.
世界に打ちのめされて負ける意味を知った
Beaten down by the world, I learned what it means to lose.
紅蓮の華よ咲き誇れ!
Crimson lotus, bloom in full pride!
運命を照らして
Shine light upon destiny!
イナバカリの雑音が耳を刺す
The noise of lightning strikes pierces my ears.
惑う心 優しいだけじゃ守れないものがある
A bewildered heart... kindness alone isn't enough to protect what matters.
わかってはいるけど
I know that, but...
水面下で絡まる善悪
Good and evil intertwined beneath the surface,
透けて見える偽善に天罰
divine punishment upon transparent hypocrisy.
Tell me why, tell me why, tell me why, tell me why
I don't need you
逸材の花より
Rather than a single flawless flower,
挑み続け咲いた一輪が美しい
a single blossom that keeps struggling to bloom is beautiful.
乱暴に敷き詰められた
Roughly paved,
トゲだらけの道も
a path full of thorns
本気の僕だけに現れるから
appears only before the earnest me,
乗り越えてみせるよ
so I will overcome it!
簡単に片付けられた
Easily brushed aside,
守れなかった夢も
even the dreams I failed to protect
紅蓮の心臓に根を生やし
take root in this crimson heart,
この血に宿ってる
dwelling within this blood.
人知れず脆い
Secretly fragile,
散りゆく結末
an ending that scatters away.
無情に破れた
Heartlessly torn,
悲鳴の風吹く
a screaming wind blows.
誰かの笑う影
Someone's laughing shadow,
誰かの泣き声
someone's crying voice...
誰もが幸せを願っている
Everyone is wishing for happiness.
どうしたって!
No matter what!
消せない夢も 止まれない今も
With dreams I can't erase and a present I can't stop,
誰かのために強くなれるなら
if I can grow stronger for someone else's sake,
ありがとう 悲しみよ
thank you, sadness.
世界に打ちのめされて負ける意味を知った
Beaten down by the world, I learned what it means to lose.
紅蓮の華よ咲き誇れ!
Crimson lotus, bloom in full pride!
運命を照らして
Shine light upon destiny!
Oh no...
Everything is burned down!
My house and the entire village is destroyed!
What is going on?
Are you all right?
A giant monster...
...burned down my entire village with its fire breath!
That is bad!
Do you know where that monster is heading?
I think it's headed to the next village.
Don't worry!
I shall take care of it for you, so it won't destroy the other village too.
In order to do that,
I need to collect power by singing and music.
So please,
lend me your power, oh dear villager!
Oh, I will!
星を回せ 世界の真ん中で
Spin the stars right in the center of the world
くしゃみすれば
If I sneeze
どこかの森で 蝶が乱舞
butterflies dance wildly in some forest.
キミが守る ドアの鍵
The key to the door that you protect
デタラメ
is absolute nonsense,
恥ずかしい物語
an embarrassing story.
舐め合っても
Even if we lick each other's wounds,
ライオンは強い
the lion is strong.
生き残りたい
I want to survive!
まだ生きてたくなる
I still want to go on living.
星座の導きで
Guided by the constellations,
今 見つめ合った
our eyes met just now.
生き残りたい
I want to survive,
途方に暮れて
at my wit's end,
キラリ枯れてく
fading away with a glimmer.
本気のカラダ見せつけるまで
Until I show you my true body,
私眠らない
I will not sleep.
風はやがて
The wind will eventually
東へ向かうだろう
head east.
高気圧 この星の
High pressure attacks
氷河を襲う
this planet's glaciers.
誘い水を飲んだ
My chest aches from
胸がつらい
drinking the enticement water,
遠吠えな物語
a distant howling story.
かじり合う
Biting each other
骨の奥まで
deep down to the bones.
生き残りたい
I want to survive!
まだ生きてたくなる
I still want to go on living.
星座の導きで
Guided by the constellations,
今 見つめ合った
our eyes met just now.
生き残りたい
I want to survive,
途方に暮れて
at my wit's end,
キラリ枯れてく
fading away with a glimmer.
本気のカラダ見せつけるまで
Until I show you my true body,
私眠らない
I will not sleep.
Wish to survive
何しに生まれたの？
Why was I born?
何しにここにいる？
Why am I here?
生き残りたい
I want to survive!
埋まらない傷 光恐れてた
Fearing unhealable wounds and the light,
許されたい生命が今 惹かれ合った
the lives that wish to be forgiven are now drawn to each other.
さまよい果てて
Wandering to the end,
君のとなりで ほてり鎮めたい
beside you, I want to soothe this fever.
本気のカラダ見せつけるまで
Until I show you my true body,
私眠らない
I will not sleep.
生き残りたい
I want to survive,
崖っぷちでいい
being on the edge is fine,
君を愛してる
I love you!
目覚めたい生命が今 惹かれ合った
The lives that wish to awaken are now drawn to each other.
狂気に変えて
Turning it into madness,
祈り捧ぐよ
I offer a prayer,
君を愛してる
I love you.
星座の導きで...
Guided by the constellations...
生き残りたい
I want to survive!
まだ生きてたい
I still want to live!
君を愛してる
I love you!
本気のココロ見せつけるまで
Until I show you my true heart,
私眠らない
I will not sleep!
星が降る
Stars Are Falling
羽根もない
Without even wings,
この私（わたくし）が
I...
憧れてた
longed for
あの空
that sky.
背伸びして
Standing on tiptoe,
星をつかむ
trying to reach the stars,
真似をしてみた
I pretended to reach out.
負けないで
Don't give in...
願いさえも
even as the darkness
飲み込む闇
swallows up every wish.
それでも
Even so,
ただぐるぐる回る
Just spinning round and round
車輪の中で
inside the wheel...
走っても 走っても
No matter how much I run,
たどり着けなくて
I can never reach anywhere.
先を行く君の
Watching your back
背中ばかりを見ていた
as you walked ahead of me...
いつか超えられる
Someday I'll surpass you,
もっと強くなりたい
I want to become so much stronger!
ひとり生まれてきた
Born into this world alone,
その記憶もなくして
with even those memories lost...
泣き声も届かないと
Crying out, but my voice doesn't reach,
嘆いてみても
even as I grieve...
信じていた
I believed in
大きな木に
the great tree,
しがみついた
clinging onto it,
爪痕
leaving my mark...
あの空へ
Towards that sky,
近づくこと
getting closer...
分かっているから
because I know!
風が雲を
The wind...
流して
blows the clouds away,
星が降る
stars come falling down.
羽根もない
Without even wings,
この私（わたくし）が
I...
憧れてた
longed for
あの空
that sky.
背伸びして
Standing on tiptoe,
星をつかむ
trying to reach the stars,
真似をしてみた
I pretended to reach out.
負けないで
Don't give in...
願いさえも
even as the darkness
飲み込む闇
swallows up every wish.
それでも
Even so,
手探りで
fumbling in the dark,
夢のカケラ
pieces of my dream—
集めに行くよ
I'm going to gather them up!
I think after all this singing,
my power is still not enough to defeat the giant pink monster!
I heard you, young warrior.
I can help you with your worry.
As I,
the keeper of the legendary weapon Nut Blade,
will lend you its power!
Is this...
the voice of the Fire Blade Priestess?
Yes, you are right.
I will lend you the power of this Nut Blade
if you can prove yourself that you have the spirit
to fight the pink giant monster!
Ah, okay!
(Why?) 胸に刻めよ 時代のリーダー
(Why?) Engrave it in your heart, the leader of the era
(Who?) 見ためよりかは かなりクレーバー
(Who?) Much cleverer than they look
(Fool!) 乾いた心 すさむよりは
(Fool!) Rather than letting a dry heart go cold
(Fight!) 時に泣いてみれば 見えてくる
(Fight!) If you try crying sometimes, you'll start to see
明日駆けるのは
What runs toward tomorrow
紛れもなく新しい自分
is undoubtedly a new version of yourself.
誰のためでもなく
Not for anyone else's sake,
ただもっと上を目指せ
just aim even higher!
Dragon Screamer!
昇る龍のようだ
Like a rising dragon
金の光が呼んだ未来が
The future called by the golden light
導くんだ 僕らを
will guide us!
Dragon Screamer! Dragon Fever! No question!
(Why?) 見えているのに はるかなゴールは
(Why?) Though visible, the goal is so far away
(Where?) 見ためよりかは かなり HARDER
(Where?) Much harder than it looks
(Hard!) 君が踏み出す 勇気持てば
(Hard!) If you have the courage to step forward
(Fight!) やがて開く道が
(Fight!) Eventually, the opening path
目指すべき場所選ぶのは
The one choosing the destination to aim for
紛れもなく新しい自分
is undoubtedly a new version of yourself.
翼を手にした君は
Having gained wings, you
どんな山をも越える
will overcome any mountain!
Dragon Screamer!
叫ぶ龍のような
Like a roaring dragon
銀の嵐が吹き飛ばすんだ
The silver storm blows away
迷いとか 恐れを
all hesitation and fear!
Dragon Screamer! Dragon Fever! No question!
Oh my way 走り出せ! 駆け抜けてくライバルという風
Oh my way, start running! Rushing past like a wind called rivals
In that case 気持ち Hi-Pace で征す
In that case, conquer with a high-pace mindset!
光りさす明日 まだ見ぬ上目指す
A shining tomorrow, aiming higher than ever seen before
諦めず探し続ける Finally
Never giving up, continuing to search, finally
いつまでも変わらぬ夢 Victory
An unchanging dream forever, victory!
空に浮かぶ Dragon
A dragon floating in the sky
背中に光りさす明日 世界をその手に
A shining tomorrow on its back, take the world in your hands!
Dragon Screamer!
昇る龍のようだ
Like a rising dragon
金の光が呼んだ未来が
The future called by the golden light
導くんだ 僕らを
will guide us!
Dragon Screamer! Dragon Fever! No question!
Dragon Screamer!
叫ぶ龍のような
Like a roaring dragon
銀の嵐が吹き飛ばすんだ
The silver storm blows away
迷いとか 恐れを
all hesitation and fear!
Dragon Screamer! Dragon Fever! No question!
You have proven me your spirit.
I shall bestow upon you the Nut Blade.
Thank you!
I shall use this weapon to defeat the monster!
Now I have the Nut Blade,
I shall continue my journey to defeat the giant pink monster!
If my hunch was right,
I think...
I should go through the forest next.
Oh no! What happened to you, Oh Mighty Dragon?
ピンクの巨人にやられた。今は力が入らん。
I was beaten by a pink giant. Right now, I have no strength.
すぐ破壊されてしまった。
I was destroyed in an instant.
Oh no, that is bad!
I can help you recover if you can take me straight to the giant monster in exchange!
任せておけ。
Leave it to me.
偶然から始まる 必然のワンシーン
A chance meeting, a scene of inevitable fate.
遠くに見えたのは 揺れる赤色
Far away, a swaying red.
不思議な森の奥で 見つけた黒い影と
Deep within the mysterious forest, a black shadow found,
何かが始まる予感 怖くて逃げ出した
A premonition of something beginning, frightened, I ran away.
「出会い」は終わりへ 続くシナリオ
"Encounters" are scenarios leading to an end.
だから わざと 遠回りをした
That's why I purposely took the long way around.
会いたいなんて 触れたいなんて 話したいなんて思わない
Wanting to see you, wanting to touch you, wanting to talk to you—I don't think like that.
かよわい君と 狡い僕が 「出会う」 其れが終わりのさ
A frail you and a sly me "meeting"—that is the end.
残酷だって罵ったって 運命は変わらない
No matter how cruelly you curse it, destiny will not change.
ああ どうして 君が？ どうして 僕が？ おおかみと赤ずきん なんだ？
Ah, why you? Why me? A wolf and Little Red Riding Hood, huh?
きっと君は今日も この道を訪れる
Surely you will visit this path again today,
そして僕は今日もずっと 見守るしかできない
and I can only keep watching over you as always.
君はあの木の先で いつも通り 隠れてる
You are hiding just beyond that tree, as usual.
私は気付かぬふりしたまま 通り過ぎた
I passed by, pretending not to notice.
視線は絡まない
Our gazes do not meet.
声は届かない
Our voices do not reach.
ため息だけが むなしく重なる
Only sighs emptyly overlap.
会えなくたって 触れなくたって 話せなくたっていいから
Even if we can't meet, touch, or talk, that's fine.
頼りない君と ぎこちない僕が そこにいるだけでいいんだ
A dependable-less you and an awkward me—just being there is enough.
これが恋だって言わないなら 言葉なんて なくってい
If this isn't called love, then words aren't needed at all.
ああ 考えたって 考えたって エンディングは変わらない
Ah, no matter how much I think, how much I ponder, the ending won't change.
会いたかったんだ 触れたかったんだ 話したかった ほんとは
I wanted to meet you, I wanted to touch you, I wanted to talk to you, really.
かわいい君と やさしい僕が 出会い 結ばれるエンド
You, so cute, and me, so gentle, meeting and being bound together—an ending.
何回だって 何回だって 神様に願ったよ
Many times over, many times over, I prayed to God.
でも... かなしいくらい かなしいくらい おおかみと赤ずきん なんだ
But... sadly, oh so sadly, we are a wolf and Little Red Riding Hood.
泣いてる君をなぐさめたくて 伸ばした腕が ふるえる
Wanting to comfort you as you cry, my outstretched arms tremble.
愛しているよ 抱きしめたいよ だけど できないんだよ...！
I love you, I want to hold you close, but I can't...!
どうあがいたって どう願ったって 爪も牙も消えない
No matter how I struggle, no matter what I wish for, my claws and fangs won't disappear.
だから ただ待ってるよ 君の涙が止むまで
So I will just wait, until your tears stop,
あの木の先で ずっと...
just beyond that tree, forever...
Ah, here you go! If you eat this, you can recover super quick!
感謝する。
Thank you.
よし、完全回復だ。
Alright, I am fully recovered.
今すぐ怪獣のもとへ案内しよう。
I will guide you to the monster immediately.
Okay, let's go!
飛べ FLY HIGH!! 汗と血と涙で
Fly, FLY HIGH!! With sweat, blood, and tears
飛べ FLY HIGH!!
Fly high!!
汗と血と涙で光る翼で
With sweat, blood, and tears, on shining wings,
いま 全部 全部 置き去って
now leave everything, everything behind.
飛べ FLY
Fly high,
高く FLY
fly higher
最果ての未来へ
to the furthest future.
傷だらけの若鳥が空を睨んでる
A wounded young bird glares at the sky.
低空飛行する奴等が嗤おうと
Even if those flying at low altitudes mock it,
海の果てが見たい
it wants to see the end of the sea.
心を無にして 向かい風に乗り
Empty your mind, ride the headwind,
助走をつけて
and take a run-up.
踏切・加速・跳躍(ホップ・ステップ・ジャンプ)で
With a hop, step, and jump.
飛べ FLY HIGH!! 汗と血と涙で
Fly high!! With sweat, blood, and tears,
光る翼が 君を何処へだって連れて行く
shining wings will take you anywhere.
青い衝動と本能と 爪牙(そうが)を剥き出しにして
Exposing your blue impulse, instinct, and fangs,
艱難(かんなん)の旅路も 夢叶うまで何度だって
through difficult journeys, until your dream comes true.
飛べ FLY
Fly high,
高く FLY
fly higher
最果ての未来へ
to the furthest future.
ぽつり 降り出した雨が翼狂わせる
Rain begins to fall quietly, driving the wings mad.
行く手には黒い雲
Black clouds lie ahead,
いま 長い嵐の夜が来る
and a long stormy night is coming now.
轟く雷鳴と 砕ける波濤を
Taking the roaring thunder and crashing waves
喝采にして
as applause,
一速・二速・三速(アン・ドゥ・トロワ)で
with one, two, three.
飛べ FLY HIGH!!
Fly high!!
いつも胸の奥を焦がす焔が 路を照らし出す灯台になる
The flame that burns deep in your chest becomes a lighthouse.
夜明け前の光芒が 才能の華咲かすから
Because the pre-dawn light makes talent bloom,
命尽きるまで 限界を超え最高速で
until life ends, exceed limits at maximum speed,
飛べ FLY
fly high.
飛べ FLY HIGH!!
Fly high!!
汗と血と涙で光る翼が 君を何処へだって連れて行く
Shining wings of sweat, blood, and tears will take you anywhere.
青い衝動と本能と 爪牙(そうが)を剥き出しにして
Exposing your blue impulse, instinct, and fangs,
全部 全部 置き去って
leave everything, everything behind.
飛べ FLY HIGH!!
Fly high!!
いつも胸の奥を焦がす焔が 路を照らし出す灯台になる
The flame that burns deep in your chest becomes a lighthouse.
夜明け前の光芒が 才能の華咲かすから
Because the pre-dawn light makes talent bloom,
命尽きるまで 限界を超え最高速で
until life ends, exceed limits at maximum speed,
飛べ FLY
fly high,
高く FLY
fly higher
最果ての未来へ
to the furthest future.
It's over now, evil monster!
I have the high ground!
If I love you, would you love me too
...would you love me too?
Utara ku kecil dahulu
My northern star when I was small
The love will last, it will
Selamanya 'ku 'kan peduli
Forever, I will care
Right through me
Broken thing have I become
A broken thing have I become
And you see, life is pain
Truly I, I just never had enough
Ordinary day it seems, the clouds of love
On an ordinary day, it seems the clouds of love
In the sky painted colors in my paradise
Titik hujan menyegarkan segala
Raindrops refresh everything
Bunga-bunga emosi manusia
The flowers of human emotion
Mekar dan berkembang megah selamanya
Bloom and flourish grandly forever
Will I love you like you love me too?
Utara mu lebih dahulu
Your northern star came first
The love will last, it will
Selamanya 'ku 'kan ada di sini
Forever, I will be here
To me, enchanting have I become
And you see, life is fair
Truly I am enough
Ordinary day it seems, the cloud of lies
On an ordinary day, it seems the cloud of lies
In the sky painted color in my paradise
Titik hujan menghapuskan segala
Raindrops wipe away everything
Luka duka emosi manusia
The pain and grief of human emotion
Rapuh dan terjatuh, lelah di dunia
Fragile and fallen, weary of this world
The halo lingers on my ego
Blinding light that radiates evaporates the sad in me
Blinding light that radiates evaporates the sadness in me
A soundless whisper, follow me
Never let go
Bahagia jadi nyata, hal nyata berdua
Happiness becomes real, something real between us two
To me, obsessive have I become
And you see, life is fair
Never I had enough
Never have I had enough
Ordinary I will be, the cloud and the color of rainbow
Start to show in my paradise
Titik hujan meleburkan segala
Raindrops melt away everything
Luka duka emosi manusia
The pain and grief of human emotion
Rapuh dan terlalu lelah di dunia
Fragile and far too weary of this world
Hi, finally I can see you
Awan gelap yang membentuk aku
Dark clouds that shaped who I am
Titik hujan membasuh
Raindrops wash over
Suka dan duka perasaan
The joy and sorrow of feelings
Dan melebur menjadi satu warna yang bermakna
Melting together into a single meaningful color
Stop right there!
I'm here to stop you and release all the Nut Nuts from misery!
Woah! I can't believe...
...that we've defeated the giant monster!
It's actually this cute! Aw~
As a celebration, let's sing one more song!
ひらひら 葉落月
Fluttering leaf-fall moon,
夜明けが見たいって 叫んだ空
the sky cried out that it wanted to see the dawn.
暗く暗く陰と影の死の夜も
Even in the dark, dark night of shade and shadow death,
深く深く耐えて芽差す地の慈よ
enduring deeply, the grace of the earth sprouts forth.
来たる光照らす新世の世に
Into the new world illuminated by the coming light,
高く高く舞え ヒバリ
soar high, high up, skylark!
神様気取りのマダム達が 世界をA.I.して壊しました
Madams playing God loved the world with AI and destroyed it.
誰のもの誰のもの我のもの 邪魔者は排除した
"Whose is it? Whose is it? It's mine!" They eliminated all obstacles.
カントがなんとか言ってたって エゴに掴まれて拒めないんだ
No matter what Kant said, caught by ego, we cannot refuse.
まだ足りない物足りない死にたくない
Still not enough, not satisfied, I don't want to die!
機械仕掛けの狂った声で大人達が言う
Adults speak with clockwork, crazy voices:
we doin' holy war for luv
"We're doing a holy war for love."
うんざりだよ
I'm sick of it.
シンドローム：アイシテル
Syndrome: "I love you."
あぁ もうやめてよ
Ah, please stop it already!
心ってモノを量って切って 売れば幸せですか？
Are you happy measuring, cutting, and selling what's called a heart?
造られた憧憬 もう抜け出したい欺瞞世界虚空の果て
Fabricated longing, I want to break free from this deceitful world at the end of void.
魂を一体どこに隠した？
Where on earth did you hide your soul?
神よ、科学よ、イヴよ
Oh God, oh science, oh Eve!
天つ少女詩と舞う
Heavenly maiden dances with song,
ヒバリの天
under the skylark's sky.
「輪廻転生 機械論 進化の論 人が人でなく堕ち無くなる地に片喰よ怺えろと
"Samsara, mechanism, evolution... when humans fall and perish from the earth, endure, creeping woodsorrel...
歌だけは未来へ届くよう
So that at least songs reach the future,
天から空へと繋げるよう
So that heaven connects to sky,
限りなく鳴く光ヒバリ達を遺す」
Leaving behind the endlessly singing skylarks of light."
なんて絵本を聞かせてくれたっけ ねぇ リリアン
Wasn't that the picture book you read to me? Hey, Lilian...
「2人のこと愛してる」 嘘でもいいから一度だけでも聞かせてよ！
"I love you two." Even if it's a lie, let me hear it just once!
常世ってトコで笑ってますか？ 今は幸せですか？
Are you smiling in the everlasting land? Are you happy now?
置き去りのまま
Left behind like this,
届かない想い「ごめん」なんて言えなかったかな
unreachable feelings... I wonder if I couldn't even say "I'm sorry."
悲しい思い出は風に隠した
I hid my sad memories in the wind.
歌よ、あなたの元へ
Oh song, go to where you are.
天つ少女時を舞う
Heavenly maiden dances through time,
ヒバリの天
under the skylark's sky.
ひとりでも笑って生きるんだ
Even alone, I'll live with a smile.
ひとりでは生きていけないんだ
I can't go on living alone.
ずっと拒んだり愛したり 恨んで壊してそれても
Forever rejecting, loving, resenting, destroying... Even so,
縋って生きるよ
I'll cling on and live.
心ってモノを量って切って 売れば幸せですか？
Are you happy measuring, cutting, and selling what's called a heart?
造られたshowcase もう逃げ出せない期待未来奇跡の鍵
Fabricated showcase, key to expected future and miracles I can't escape from anymore.
魂を一体どこに隠した？
Where on earth did you hide your soul?
神よ、科学よ、イヴよ
Oh God, oh science, oh Eve!
天つ少女詩と舞う
Heavenly maiden dances with song,
夜明けを告げたら いこう
Once dawn is proclaimed, let's go,
ヒバリの天
under the skylark's sky.
Hi everyone! Woo!
Now, now, now...
How was my performance? Do you like it?
Did you guys have fun?
And also, for celebrating my victory and my birthday...
we have special merch! Yes!
So, here's the merch! Woohoo!
Whoa! How cool is it?
And it's not only cool,
this year's merch was designed to be useful too.
So let's have a closer look, shall we?
First up...
Ooh! Whoa!
It's an awesome A3 tapestry drawn by netural-sensei! Woah!
The whole illustration just...
woah, it looks super awesome! It looks so cool!
You can see that I'm holding my beloved...
mhm, just look at that! Warrior Risu with full dark side! Isn't that awesome? Woo!
Don't miss it!
And also, don't forget, you guys gotta buy it at least five, okay?
And I think let's see what we have next!
Woo! A super cute tumbler for everybody!
So you guys, uh, won't forget to hydrate!
Um, you can use it to drink water,
and you can use it pretty much always.
So be sure to use it every day, okay?
And next, we have this!
Whoa! A Smartphone Ring!
Ooh! So you can be, um, super comfortable and remember me when you're, um, holding your phone.
And it also will secure your phone in your hand.
Very, very convenient.
And I think let's see the full set now! Woo!
Whoa, there's so much stuff, actually.
And also, don't forget, we have the full set purchase bonus here!
So, I will explain it a little bit.
Uh, for those of you who purchase the full set will also receive a signed, foil-stamped postcard!
And for my super Risunuts who purchase the Limited Edition full set will receive a postcard autographed by none other than me! Autographed by me!
Isn't it awesome? Wow!
And the pre-order window is only a month, so make sure that you don't miss it!
Oh, oh, oh, oh! Also one more thing!
Did you guys listen to my new original song 'Hoshi ga Furu'?
It will be officially released after this stream at midnight JST. JST, okay? On my YouTube channel!
So go listen to it, and...
maybe who knows that later we will have MV for it? I don't know!
And last but not least, for all of you who joined my membership, you don't want to miss a special additional 3D performance in membership,
just right after this show has ended!
If you haven't joined my membership yet, do not hesitate because the extra show is going to be mind-boggling!
What are you waiting for? Join membership now!
Woo! Ooh!
Oops, but I think the time is up. Ah...
And I have to continue... But yes, I have to continue with the membership show now!
So thank you so much, everyone, for your support for this whole six years, especially!
And thank you for celebrating my birthday together with me!
So...
Bye-bye, everyone! Otsurisuu!
The Rise of the Nut Warrior